[♪♪♪]
[WAVES CRASHING]
SAM:
60% of all professional killers
grow a conscience
as mid-life approaches,
but in my line of work,
there's no such thing
as a retirement plan.
Instead, you get me.
[GUNSHOTS]
[♪♪♪]
[CARTRIDGE AND HAMMER CLICKING]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
Turn around.
Put your weapon down.
I got a deal for you.
You walk away, you live.
SAM:
Hold up.
Let's go back a bit,
see how we got here.
My mark is an assassin
who disappeared on the job
a few years ago.
He's been a tough one to find.
Turns out he's now
an art dealer for exclusive--
Let's just say
not exactly legal pieces.
Because of that,
he only takes meetings
from referrals he trusts.
And it just so happens
the dirt bag I'm gonna see
now is a direct line to him.
Now I don't usually
involve civilians
or anyone outside my target,
but this guy,
he's a grade A piece of shit.
He sells women, drugs, guns,
even kids
to the ultra-wealthy.
I'm gonna be doin'
the world a favor.
[♪♪♪]
-[MUFFLED GUNSHOT]
-[GROANS]
[♪♪♪]
[MUFFLED GUNSHOTS]
[MESSAGES BEEPING]
[CAR WHOOSHES]
SAM:
My job is to find and eliminate
retired assets.
I don't care how long it takes,
I will finish the job.
I kill the best of the best.
I'm an assassin of assassins,
a killer of killers.
I didn't just fall
into this profession
like so many others,
I was an orphan of circumstance.
I chose to hunt down the most
dangerous people on the planet,
and make it my life's work,
and I take great pride
in what I do.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN BACKGROUND]
[GATE CLUNKS]
Good morning,
I'm Mr. Anthony.
Beautiful home.
Yes, it is.
It's my retirement home.
You're retired?
I am. I am.
Um, but it didn't suit me well.
I understand that.
I don't think
I could ever retire.
Well...
Would you like to sit?
Thank you.
[GLASSES CLINKING]
So tell me exactly
what you're looking for.
A Rembrandt.
I think I have two of those.
I'm not looking
for just any Rembrandt.
There's one in particular.
You know which one?
Sea of Galilee.
[LAUGHS]
You might as well be looking
for Christ.
Everybody's looking
for that one.
No one's found it.
Yeah. But I think I just did.
You're not who
I thought you were.
No, I'm not.
How'd you find me?
It wasn't as hard as you think.
But why, after five years,
you come looking for me
after all this time?
The way I see it,
we're both professionals.
Or you were.
Consider this a courtesy.
If I was ever in your position,
I'd want the same thing.
Don't you ever get tired
of this job?
No.
But I'm not you,
and all those things
that you've done.
That's why I'm here.
Hmm.
[HAMMER CLICKS]
You younger breed,
you know nothing,
you never have an exit strategy.
Too many video games.
And you older breed,
you know nothing
about technology.
[GUN MOUNT WHIRS]
-[GUNSHOT]
-[EXPLOSION]
[BULLET WHOOSHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
IN BACKGROUND]
[♪♪♪]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
IN BACKGROUND]
[HORSES GALLOPING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
AUGUSTUS:
Yes.
400 fuckin' thousand dollars
to win.
If I wanted across the board,
I'd have fuckin' said it!
All of it, to win!
[CROWD CLAMORING IN BACKGROUND]
You bet on Bing Bong Bing?
Gambling isn't exactly
advisable in my line of work.
Well, suit yourself.
But I've got a feelin'
this long shot's
gonna come through.
I bet on a sure thing.
I assume you received
your instructions okay.
SAM:
I did.
I'll take care
of the accommodations myself.
I'll be in touch.
Mr. Hayden, when I put
my money down on anything,
it's never a gamble.
I bet on a sure thing.
SAM:
Augustus is a smug prick,
but he's also my boss.
He runs what we call
the "organization".
It's a loose net
of wealthy gangsters
who control a vast network
of assassins for hire.
I'm an assassin,
but I only kill wolves
to protect the sheep.
Every assignment
has its pros and cons.
The pros of this one,
the target's hiding out
right on my doorstep
and I get to make
a long overdue trip home.
The cons? This motherfucker.
Charles Managold.
Now, I don't get nervous
or intimidated
by any target because,
well, I'm the best.
But if I did,
Managold would do it.
[PLANE WHOOSHES]
SAM: A born killer
who won't let anything
or anyone stand in his way.
He doesn't care who or where.
If he accepts the contract,
someone's gonna die.
Now he's my contract.
How the hell did this happen?
[DETECTOR BLIPPING]
[♪♪♪]
Fuckin' tracker.
Really, Augustus?
[TRACKER THUDDING]
Prick.
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS]
[CAR ENGINE WHIRS]
SAM:
Mine is a nomadic existence,
and that suits me just fine,
or else I'm in the wrong line
of work.
[CAR WHOOSHES]
SAM: In this business,
you don't have friends.
You don't have relationships,
because they'll find out
and that's what gets you killed.
You can't have any weaknesses.
Weaknesses are exploited.
But everyone needs a place
to call home,
somewhere completely
off the grid
where they'll never find you.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
SAM: Somewhere that feels like
a breath of fresh air.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
[BIRDS CAWING AND CHIRPING
IN BACKGROUND]
SAM:
Somewhere to feel safe.
[♪♪♪]
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN BACKGROUND]
Finally.
Hi.
Welcome home.
It's good to be home.
I missed you.
Hmm.
Mm, you get a shower
before you get any of this.
You're gonna be
the death of me.
If you're lucky.
[DOOR OPENS]
[THUMP]
[CLUNK]
[THUS]
[CURTAIN SCRAPES]
[TAP SQUEAKS]
[WATER RUNNING]
You see who it is?
Yeah, just another cliché.
An assassin
who grew a conscience.
That's Charles Managold.
Yeah.
He's a legend.
SAM:
They all are.
NONA:
Chuparosa?
SAM:
Everyone's heard of Chuparosa.
Range, 1,900 yards.
Velocity, 2,008 feet per second.
[FRIDGE DOOR OPENS]
Bullet drop, wind speed,
curvature of the earth...
[ICE CUBES CLINK]
...all factored in.
[FRIDGE DOOR SHUTS]
Bullets don't fly straight.
It's a common misconception,
especially at that range.
They come right down
on your head.
And by doing so,
he killed an innocent woman
in the process.
Went through her
to hit his mark.
Charles Managold
would've killed his own mother
if that meant completin' a job.
[BOTTLE CLUNKS]
First off, goin' through
an innocent woman
to hit his mark
is a hell of a shot.
Second, things change.
God knows what would make
a sick fuck like that
not follow through.
He's ruthless, Sam.
I think you of all people know
how ruthless I can be, Nona.
Besides, I think
if I didn't know any better,
you're kinda worried about me.
You should try bein' afraid
more often, you know?
Nah.
You never could refuse me, Sam.
I'm the ring that's missin'
in your chain mail armor.
Your one weak spot.
I don't have a weak spot, Nona.
Hmm.
But if I did,
I think you'd be it.
[INSECTS CHIRPING]
Walk away.
NONA: I'm gonna have to take you
to Colombia.
ART DEALER:
Walk away.
Don't you ever get tired?
SAM:
It's a small world of assassins,
and among the best of us
is a mutual respect.
We may even share a drink or two
when we cross paths
out on assignment,
but business is business.
If I'm there for you,
you'll know.
Every killer I've ever killed
thought they were elite.
They all thought
no one could touch them
until I showed up.
There's a reason
I get the contract
from the organization.
Once you sign on,
there is a very
specific protocol
for getting out.
And that protocol is me.
I am the exit protocol.
And if you're my contract,
I will retire you.
This Managold,
despite his reputation,
shouldn't have been
any different,
but hindsight's 20/20.
Even if you're the best
and have toys that go boom,
like the art dealer said,
always have a backup plan.
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN BACKGROUND]
[FLAME CRACKLES]
[DOOR OPENS]
Be right back.
DANIQUE:
Hey, wait.
Hey. Come here.
How you feeling this morning?
Better.
You better?
Want me
to pick you up something?
You know what I like.
Okay. I'll see you sooner.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, be careful.
Say a little prayer for us.
Always.
[DOOR SHUTS]
[SIGHS]
[BELL DINGS]
[♪♪♪]
Please forgive me
the sins of my past,
let them not interfere
with the hopes of my future.
By calling you
my one true savior,
I really am saved.
Please protect us.
If not for me,
then do it for her.
Please protect her.
Amen.
Bik'egu'indán.
It's the Apache Christ.
It's how they see themselves
in him.
I know that.
Not even God
will protect you in here.
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS, PANTS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[CARTRIDGE AND HAMMER CLICKING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
Turn around.
Put your weapon down.
I coulda killed you outside
the church before you came in.
Got a deal for you.
You walk away, you live.
[BODY THUDS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[CAR ENGINE WHIRS]
Shit.
[PANTS]
[CAR TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
AUGUSTUS:
Five minutes out.
He should be finished
by the time we get there.
A little unusual,
you joining us in the field.
You tryin' to get
your combat experience?
I'd rather be feeding
my fuckin' horses,
but we have an important client.
Wicked.
Isaac.
We're not gonna have
a problem here, are we?
Have I ever?
No, but you've never
experienced anything like this.
Like what?
Personal.
I'd be offended
if I didn't think
you were joking.
[SIGHS]
She can be a little feisty,
even on a regular day.
I prefer to think of it
as passion forward.
ISAAC:
Hmm.
Like the oak
of a well-crafted bourbon.
Wicked, I'm serious.
Be on your best behavior.
You don't have to worry
about me, Isaac.
All business.
[CAR WHOOSHES]
[♪♪♪]
Danique!
Danique?
[WATER RUNNING IN BACKGROUND]
Come on, we gotta go now.
Let's go.
What?
Get dressed, we gotta go.
Charles, what's going on?
[TAP SQUEAKS]
CHARLES:
We gotta leave now.
Is it the Bashkim crew?
Did they find us?
It's just one man. Get dressed.
Fuck!
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[BAG RUFFLES]
[THUMP]
[ZIPPER ZIPS]
[CASH RUSTLING]
What are we gonna do?
Don't worry about it.
Let's get out of here.
All our things and--
Are replaceable, you're not.
Let's go.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Fuck!
CHARLES:
Come on, let's go.
WICKED: Do you think he still
keeps my picture in his wallet
or should I just carve my name
in his chest to remind him?
Wicked, is it?
This is very important.
Can you please stay on task?
Important to you, not me.
I work for Isaac.
Wicked.
I'm just messin' around.
Tuggin' on your boss's strings
a bit.
You like a good tug, right?
Where the fuck
did you find her at?
A story for another time.
In the dark corners of hell
that are your fantasies, baby.
You're more like
the burn in my throat
from the cheap shit
I drank in high school.
You know, I've been working
with you for almost a year
and you still surprise me.
I had no idea
you had any education.
[LAUGHS]
Fuck you, college girl.
Careful, Dax, you might end up
like all her exes.
All except for one, huh?
Oof, his time is coming.
Mm-hmm.
You went to college?
Magna cum laude.
Dangerous world
makes a dangerous girl.
[DART WHOOSHES]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[BOLT CLICKS]
DANIQUE:
What?
Let's go.
Okay.
[PANTING]
Fuck, the tires!
[GUNSHOTS]
[PANTS]
I could've killed you
in church.
I think you owe me
the same professional courtesy.
That's not how this works.
Your weaknesses aren't mine.
But whatever happens,
don't hurt the girl.
Civilians aren't my thing.
Last I checked,
that's your signature.
Yeah, I know all about Mexico.
What's he talkin' about?
Shh.
So what happened?
Feel guilty about the senorita?
So you fell
for the next pretty mark?
That sounded about right?
That, and I found God, remember?
It must suck
being so predictable.
[MACHINE GUN SHOTS]
[GROANS]
Stay down.
Friends of yours?
I don't think so.
[MACHINE GUN FIRING]
Look...
[PANTS]
...any chance
we could finish your shit
some other time?
What's the rush?
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROANS]
30 seconds out,
they met resistance.
I thought you said
there wouldn't be
any fucking complications.
[BOLT CLICKS]
Just stay behind us.
We'll clean it up.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[DISTANT GUNSHOTS]
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS]
[CAR ENGINE WHIRS]
Seriously?
Your boss, not mine.
Let's go.
[GUNSHOTS]
[♪♪♪]
[CAR WINDOW SHATTERS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROANING]
On me. Ready?
Go!
[GUNSHOTS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[GROANS]
We're in trouble.
It's Isaac.
Oh, fuck.
Who's Isaac?
Isaac Florentine,
he's the typical
one-man army type.
But today, clearly,
he's probably
the second-best assassin
in the world.
Who's the first?
-Me.
-SAM: Me.
[GUNSHOTS]
Good to see you again, Managold.
You're a fuckin' legend.
Shame.
Yeah, good to see you, too.
Hey, Hayden.
It's been a minute.
You here to pay me back
for that drink in Havana?
Maybe another time.
But you know if you're
not willin' to do your job,
you're gonna force me
to do mine.
Unfortunately,
I've already promised you
to someone else.
Hey, Hayden.
Oh, fuck.
Is that Wicked?
SAM:
Yeah.
Is someone actually
named Wicked?
Yeah. Name fits.
Yes, her real name's Annie.
We had a thing a few years ago.
It was fun.
You left me at the altar!
Let's see how you like this one.
Yeah, sorry about that!
It was Vegas.
Wicked?
I'm gonna fuckin' cut
your balls off!
[GUNSHOTS]
Shit!
[EXPLOSION]
Oh, fuck!
Let's go, let's go. Let's go.
Let's go, come on.
[PANTING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN BACKGROUND]
[♪♪♪]
Come on.
[GRUNTS]
All business, huh? Come on.
[DOOR OPENS]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
I need water.
Okay.
There's some water over here.
Let's go.
[PANTING]
[WATER RUNS]
You okay?
Yeah.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
Here, just take it.
Get rest here.
[PANTS]
[GROANS]
Hey!
That was for the church.
What the hell
is Isaac doing here?
DANIQUE: Oh, fuck.
He's here for the girl.
She witnessed a murder
in London.
The organization wanted
to get rid of her,
and I got the call.
Bashkim and the Albanians,
a messy job.
CHARLES:
Yeah.
But you couldn't go through
with it?
I wouldn't have done it
any different.
You think you know
all about me?
I know about you, too.
I know how they contracted you.
I know about that girl.
[PANTING]
But I finished that job.
I always finish a job.
Wait! I'm pregnant.
I don't make exceptions.
Okay.
Well, do what you gotta do then.
Huh?
[GROANS]
Fuck.
CHARLES:
What is it? What's wrong?
Okay, one second.
Get some water.
Get some-- get some water.
[WATER RUNNING]
[PANTING]
CHARLES: Breathe, breathe.
Breathe, breathe.
Okay, let's just take care
of the-- shh, shh, shh.
[PANTING]
SAM: Bashkim is a client.
That's not good.
[CAR WHOOSHES]
SAM: Not exactly someone you
wanna meet in a dark alley,
an enforcer who rose
through the ranks
because of his brutality,
and now runs the Albanians.
I underestimated Managold
at the church.
He's a legend for a reason.
You don't give guys like him
an inch, and that was my fault.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
SAM: But I would've
had himat the house
if Isaac didn't show up.
What the hell is he doin' here?
This is my job.
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN AND SHUTS]
[LID CLUNKS]
I swore I would never do this.
I said, "Sam, you will always
finish the job."
[CARTRIDGE CLICKS]
But now here we are.
[BOLT CLICKS]
I swore I would never do this.
I swore I would finish the job.
I swear I never missed my mark.
And he deserved it, right?
Everybody I killed has.
Everybody?
You saw yourself
in that target, didn't you?
Where you could've been?
No, no, no, no.
I don't miss a mark.
Then tell Augustus
you need more time.
Tell him Managold got away
from you.
You did underestimate him, love.
I'm gonna finish this.
[CAR WHIRS]
[PHONE RINGS]
[AUGUSTUS ON PHONE]
How's the weather where you are?
I need more time.
AUGUSTUS: [ON PHONE]
More time? You?
Yeah, shit happens.
Shit hasn't happened
in 12 years.
[SAM ON PHONE] Exactly,
so why was Isaac there?
AUGUSTUS: [ON PHONE]
Managold isn't just any target.
The client demanded the best.
I am the best.
Then prove it!
[DISCONNECT TONE]
[PHONE KEYS CLICK]
Fucking prick.
SAM:
I'm spiraling.
What the hell
is happening to me?
[CROWS CAWING IN BACKGROUND]
SAM:
Why can't I finish this job?
I should just shoot him
and be done with it.
[PLANE WHIRRING]
[SLURPS]
[CAR WHIRRING]
Drowning your sorrows?
You know I don't drink
on the job.
By the look of it,
you're not even on job anymore.
In fact, you and Managold
look real buddy-buddy,
maybe like you're
workin' together.
I don't do partners.
And I'm here to finish
what I started.
I always do.
You mean always did.
Hey, Annie.
About Vegas...
I can't wait
to fucking kill you.
I was hoping
we could talk this out.
Don't.
That weekend was...
Unless you're gonna apologize,
just stop.
I'm, um...
[SIGHS]
I...
I probably could've gone
about it differently.
That's not an apology, fuckface!
Hey, hey, hey.
As much as I'm enjoying
watching you gettin'
your balls handed to you,
I'd prefer this
not escalate any further.
Appreciate it.
I see you had
the same idea I did.
So, they didn't charter
the plane
in their real names, huh?
Bit too obvious.
How'd you know I'd be here?
Well, this airport is just
far enough away
for a small plane to make it
to Mexico on one tank.
Then go anywhere else
from there.
It's the way I'd get out.
Of course you would.
So, is this the part
where you say,
"Good to see you here, Hayden.
Think we'll step aside
and let you finish it."
You mean like you did
at the church?
You were there?
I had eyes everywhere.
He's quicker than he looks.
[CHUCKLES]
You either gettin' too cocky,
or you let him go.
I would've had him at the house
if you didn't intervene.
That's not what it looked
like to me.
Well, then you should get
your eyes checked.
Walk away, Hayden.
I'll take it from here.
I don't like people finishing
my work.
It's in good hands, though.
I'm the best in the business.
Second best.
Hardly.
Now, this is your one chance
to walk away, for better.
How kind of you.
I'll even give you
proof of death
for your employers.
You'd do that?
You know I'm a man of my word.
Proof of death
by tomorrow morning.
As soon as I have it.
And I am sorry
about killing your guys.
Seriously?
You can apologize for them,
but not to me?
You fucking asshole!
Easy. Easy.
Your day of reckoning
for killing him is not up to me,
but it's coming.
It's gonna have to get in line.
[CAR WHIRS]
[SIGHS]
Cabo or Mexico City?
Your choice.
Where do you wanna go?
Here you go.
Keep the change, buddy.
-All right.
-Good.
SAM:
Now I knew
Managold was getting sloppy.
The girl had dulled his edge,
made him miss things
that would've gotten him killed
years ago.
We gotta get out
of the country tonight.
This is the best way.
As long as we're together.
SAM: Like a spider spiraling
downa flushing toilet,
I pitied him.
Maybe that's why I let him
live the first time we met,
and that's why what I did next
confused the hell out of me.
What a fucking cliché.
[GUNSHOT]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Come on, let's go.
Let us in! Let us in!
[GUNSHOTS]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Get in!
How do we know
we can trust you?
Get in the car!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Let's get in.
Okay.
[GUNSHOTS]
CHARLES:
Get in. Get in.
[GUNSHOTS]
Okay, let's go!
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR VROOMS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[CAR WHOOSHES]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR VROOMS]
Shit.
Motherfuckers.
[PANTING]
You okay?
DANIQUE:
Uh-huh.
All right. We'll be fine.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Good.
So, why are you doin' this?
Want me to change my mind?
For fuck's sake.
We've been through
all this bullshit already.
You saved us back there.
Surely, you did it for a reason.
More like a whim.
Could've gone either direction.
Now we're all fucked.
Is this true?
Well, at least we have
the same enemies now.
[SIGHS]
So what's the plan?
I have a place we can hide out.
Okay?
Okay.
Good.
SAM: We can regroup there,
make a plan.
Okay, let's do it.
SAM: I thought I had it
all figured out.
Maybe the art dealer
was right after all,
I didn't have an exit strategy,
or worse,
maybe I'm getting tired.
[BIRDS SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
[CAR WHIRS]
[DOOR OPENS]
We'll be safe here.
So you brought your mark
to a safe house, huh?
Nice.
DANIQUE:
I like it.
Don't worry,
we'll just get some sleep,
get you out of here
in the morning, okay?
Hmm?
Baby, we can't keep running.
What are we supposed to do,
just run and keep running?
Where are we going?
What were you gonna do
before you met me?
Uh, I don't have much, but
I'm sure you're hungry, so...
Thanks.
Yeah. Take the back bedroom.
All right, let's go.
[DOOR LOCK CLUNKS]
[HOWLING IN DISTANCE]
[INSECTS CHIRPING IN BACKGROUND]
Hey.
Promise me everything's gonna
be okay.
Gonna be fine.
Everything is fine.
Just get some sleep, all right?
Relax, don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it.
[SIGHS]
[WATER RUNNING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
This is your fault, you know?
You can't blame me
because you grew a conscious.
And like my father always said,
"Everything happens
for a reason."
Yeah, well, maybe your father
was wrong.
It's when we're kids we think
our parents know everything.
He believed
people can change.
Your father was giving
life advice.
Mine was killed
by assassins, Nona.
My mother along with him.
I dedicated my life
to find those responsible,
and I did it.
You already know this.
They took from me
just like all of my marks
took something from someone.
Something they cared about.
[GROANS]
All the things that they did,
they don't just deserve
to ride off into the sunset,
get on with their lives.
They deserve to feel the pain
that they caused,
and I give it to 'em.
[♪♪♪]
Get some sleep.
[ICE CUBES CLINK]
Who were you talking to?
A ghost.
A ghost? Yeah.
Talked to a few of those myself.
That girl in Mexico.
One of many.
How's she doin'?
CHARLES:
Better.
Good.
You know they're comin'
for us, right?
Yeah. That's why I have that.
Phew. Perfect.
And I also have this.
Even better.
[TAKES DEEP BREATHS]
[BOTTLE CLUNKS, LID CLINKS]
[ICE CUBES CLINK]
Thanks.
Cheers.
[ICE CUBES CLINKING]
[SLURPS]
[CHARLES GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
You know, sometimes I think
if I would've met
Danique earlier,
a lot of people would still
be alive.
But not you, right?
[CHARLES SIGHS]
CHARLES:
Probably not.
I don't know if I had a chance
to thank you.
No, no. Don't do that.
I still haven't decided
if I'm gonna kill you or not.
Besides, I don't need
your gratitude
and I certainly don't want it.
Cheers to that.
[SLURPS]
[GRUNTS]
What do you want?
[TAKES A DEEP BREATH]
Well, I don't want you sleeping
in that room in there.
[SCOFFS]
Fair enough.
I know what you're thinkin',
that I lost my edge.
It's not that I lost it,
I just...
[TAKES A DEEP BREATH]
...no longer care if I have it.
Yeah, but without it,
how do you expect
to take care of her?
I prayed a lot. God sent you.
A fuckin' assassin.
[CHUCKLES]
What are the odds, huh?
This isn't gonna be
one of those
"he works in mysterious ways"
conversations, is it?
You don't believe in God.
It's not a matter of belief.
I've seen men pray
for God's mercy
with the barrel of a gun
in their face.
For what? They died anyway.
Now, if God's out there,
at the very least,
he doesn't give a shit about us.
I used to be just like you.
No, you are not just like me.
Our targets were different.
Yeah, well, all I cared about
was bein' the best
at what I did,
and gettin' the job done,
whatever the job was.
[SIGHS]
You know, I may not be a priest,
but I believe all sins,
even the worst,
can be wiped clean.
How convenient for men like us.
[SLURPS]
CHARLES:
God brought us together that day
in church, remember?
I failed to notice
the light of God
in the corner of your eyes,
but I knew he was there.
I never really believed in God.
For me, it was like
a switch was flipped
and I-- I changed, you know?
Maybe it was God finding me,
I don't know.
I just know I was different.
Didn't wanna be who I'd been,
who I was.
You know, most people try
to do the right thing
their whole lives,
God or no God.
I used to be just like that,...
...till I got lost
along the way, uh.
[INDISTINCT SPEECH]
If I have to repent,
pay the price,
be punished, so be it.
[SIGHS]
Look, I deserve it, I know,
but she doesn't.
She doesn't.
[SIGHS]
I, uh...
...long before
I even met Danique,
I made a choice before--
before I even knew her.
Because it was
the right thing to do.
No other reason.
Thanks.
I'll take the first watch.
[GRUNTS]
[DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS]
[♪♪♪]
[BIRDS CHIRPING IN BACKGROUND]
I know it's not Colombia,
but it's my favorite place
in the world.
I'm gonna have to take you
to Colombia.
I'm there. You tell me.
Let's go.
This lake is beautiful.
It is.
Yeah, we can't choose
where it's gonna happen,
but if I could,
I think this is where
I'd wanna die.
Right here.
Hmm. I can see why.
It's morbid. That's morbid.
I shouldn't say that.
It's all right.
Do you wanna jump in?
Hell yeah, I wanna jump in.
Do you want me
to check the water first?
I know you.
Please.
Okay.
If it's cold,
I'm keeping my britches on.
[SHE CHUCKLES]
WOMAN: Mm.
[WATER SPLASHING]
Oh, this is perfect.
Sam, come!
Sam, co--
I'm the mark?
Yeah.
[GUNSHOT]
[BODY THUDS]
SAM: No one is innocent.
No one is innocent.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[GLASS CLUNKS]
[BIRDS SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
[♪♪♪]
[CAR WHOOSHES]
WICKED:
This motherfucker.
He's not gonna fucking
get away this time.
I'll fucking cut his balls off.
This fucking guy,
I'm gonna
motherfucking kill him.
All right.
Alpha, we're left.
You guys go right.
[TRUNK SHUTS]
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
Wicked, remember when I told you
to be on your best behavior?
Yep.
Don't.
[BIRDS SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
[♪♪♪]
[ALARM BEEPING]
[PANTING]
[INDISTINCT SPEECH]
-Stay quiet.
-[MUFFLED SCREAM]
Get down, get down. Shh.
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
Stay down.
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
-[GUNSHOT]
-[BODY THUDS]
Here, take this weapon.
Safety's off.
Both hands, both hands.
[HAMMER CLICKS]
Straighten your arms.
Okay, anybody comes through
that door, you fire.
You understand?
Shoot until they go down.
Do you understand?
Not Hayden, okay?
And aim, aim straight.
Good, good, good.
Stay there.
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROANS]
[BODY THUDS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRASS RUSTLES]
-[GUNSHOTS]
-[GROANS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[KNIFE CHINKS]
[GROANS]
[BODY THUDS]
[♪♪♪]
SAM: Hmm.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm gonna play with you,
I'm gonna cut you,
and I'm gonna kill you.
I don't know if I should be
afraid or turned on.
What shall we cut first?
Are you asking
for my opinion?
[GROANS]
Let's have some fun, shall we?
[CHUCKLES]
Okay. No, no.
Oh, it's-- that's sharp.
That's...
Yeah, yeah, that's enough.
[GROANS]
[HAMMER CLICKS]
How'd you find us
so fast, Isaac?
No one knows about this place.
Did Augustus send you?
Come on, Hayden.
You know better than that.
Yeah, the organization
has two types of people.
There's the ones
that collect a paycheck,
and the ones that see it
as a religion.
Which are you?
Like I said,
I'm a man of my word,
and I don't break it
for nobody.
Not even your family
in Bisacquino, Sicily?
See, Augustus seemed to think
that when you started
a family in Sicily 10 years ago,
you might try and disappear.
So he's been watching you
ever since,
just in case you retired.
And these are the people
you're willin' to die for.
I'd never harm
your family, Isaac.
You know that.
But they would,
and they wouldn't think twice.
Did Augustus send you?
There are three contracts,
one for the girl,
one for Managold,
and one for you.
[DOOR OPENS]
Easy. Easy.
How'd you find us?
A woman made a phone call.
CHARLES:
Tell me you didn't.
I just called my aunt in Soho.
I'm all she has left.
I wanted her to know I was okay.
I know. I get it. That's how
they found us the first time.
Dammit, Danique,
I told you no phone calls!
That's how we stayed alive
this long.
You can't expect me just
to leave my family
without a trace.
That's what I expect.
Exactly what I expect
if you want to stay alive.
If you want the baby
to stay alive.
Give me that gun.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
[RINGING TONE]
[PHONE RINGS]
Yes?
ISAAC: [ON PHONE]
How's the weather back east?
Very nice.
How's the weather
where you are?
Storms for a couple of days,
but clear skies now.
AUGUSTUS: [ON PHONE]
Good. People will be pleased.
Shall I pay you a visit?
That'd be nice.
You know where to find me.
He'll be at the track tomorrow.
I know the place.
Do we have a plan?
I always have a plan.
It's what makes me the best.
Second best.
Third best.
So what now?
I think I've had
enough killin' people.
Yeah. Me, too.
I think I'll go home
and move my family.
See you around, Isaac.
I hope not.
Sorry to interrupt the bromance.
I just need a vehicle.
[KEYS JANGLING]
ISAAC:
Take the truck.
I need to stay behind
and clean up.
No thanks to you.
See you around, Isaac.
ISAAC:
See you.
Annie.
You never did apologize.
[THUMP]
SAM: I told Augustus
I never gamble,
and I certainly never bluff.
There's a first time
for everything.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[CAR WHIRRING]
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
Baby, I'm so sorry
I used the phone.
Don't worry about it.
Just don't let it happen again.
Okay?
All I need is you, and the baby.
Yeah.
[KISSING]
And the baby.
So, where are we going?
East or West?
Where do you wanna go?
I've never been
to the Grand Canyon.
Well, that's the second-most
beautiful site in the world.
[KISSING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Here he comes again.
I'll be right back.
[CAR DOOR SHUTS]
Why don't you come with us?
[SCOFFS]
As tempting as that is,
I've made my decision.
It's time to right
all the wrongs.
You really think
they're gonna believe you?
I don't know. Maybe.
As long as Bashkim
has a contract out,
they're gonna be comin'.
Just keep her someplace safe
that she can hide out.
If she can blend in,
maybe eventually
company will forget about her.
But what about you?
I'm cleanin' out my desk.
CHARLES: You really think
they're gonna let you leave?
They're not gonna let you leave.
You know that.
Maybe that's what you want.
That is what you want.
Okay. All right.
All right. Good luck, my friend.
Thank you.
Keep her safe.
I will. Good luck.
Hayden.
[CHARLES SIGHS]
I think I owe you one.
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER: [ON PA SYSTEM]
[INDISTINCT SPEECH]
I was expecting someone else.
No shit.
Iliana, grab this man a drink.
You got it, babe.
[SLAP]
You keep up with current events?
New Mexico?
[SLURPS]
Multiple deaths from gunshots.
One man in particular
had his face shot off
and was missin' an index finger.
SAM:
It's his. Check the DNA.
[SCOFFS]
Ah, that's not necessary.
I'm quite certain
this formerly belonged
to Mr. Managold.
And that tells you what exactly?
It means you've been tryin'
to make amends
for your hesitations of late.
I finished my job,
and I want you and everyone else
to let me bow out peacefully.
And the girl, Danique?
Wasn't my contract.
Do whatever you want with her.
You've seen this play out
plenty of times.
You tried to have me killed,
you fuck!
You owe me.
And unlike everyone else,
I came back here
to talk to you face-to-face.
Sam, I never pegged you
as a stupid man.
But did you really fucking think
a finger would convince us
that Charles Managold is dead?
A head,
that would've convinced me,
but a fucking finger?
[SCOFFS]
Charles Managold is dead.
Please, Sam. Don't insult me.
SAM:
This is why I don't gamble.
[GROANS]
AUGUSTUS:
Well, Sam,
we're gonna find out
where Managold is
and we're gonna have
a lot of fun while doin' it.
Fuck.
[GROANS]
Just get comfortable.
SAM: That went about
how I was expecting.
ART DEALER:
There is only one way out.
[GUNSHOT]
I'll be seeing you soon.
[LAUGHS]
[CHAIN RATTLING]
[♪♪♪]
AUGUSTUS: [ON VIDEO CALL]
Well, wake up, Hayden.
I'd like to introduce you
to someone.
The name's Bashkim.
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
[SPITS]
[CHAIN RATTLING]
AUGUSTUS: [ON VIDEO CALL]
You brought this
upon yourself, Hayden.
Tell us where Managold
and Danique are.
This is gonna hurt a lot,
Hayden.
And how much,
that's up to you.
[SPITS]
[GRUNTING]
Oh, yeah.
[CHAIN CLINKING]
AUGUSTUS: [ON VIDEO CALL]
Bring me closer.
Where are they?
Just tell us where Managold is.
[GROANS]
AUGUSTUS: [ON VIDEO CALL]
You shouldn't doubtmy resolve.
[GROANS]
Hayden, was it worth it?
WOMAN:
Was it worth it, Hayden?
I know you see yourself
as a tough guy,
but this is getting ridiculous.
[SPITS]
Ridiculous is me talkin'
to a dead person.
NONA:
Who can blame you?
Makes it easier to live
with what you did.
I don't do it 'cause it's easy,
I do it 'cause it's hard.
You killed an assassin, Sam.
I was a stone-cold killer,
just like all the others.
And the only soft spot
I ever had was you.
I wasn't supposed to fall
in love with you, not for real.
It just happened.
And I killed you anyway
just to prove I'm the best.
NONA:
An assassin of assassins.
A killer of killers.
And I threw it all away
for two people
I don't even know.
'Cause you saw in them
what we could've been.
[CHUCKLES]
What a fucking cliché.
[GROANS]
[AUGUSTUS ON VIDEO CALL]
How did you expect to
get out of this alive?
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[♪♪♪]
[SCREAMS]
[CLUNK]
[PANTING]
[SAND RUSTLES]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
[YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[CHAIN RATTLING]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
AUGUSTUS: [ON VIDEO CALL]
Bashkim? What happened?
Hayden! Hayden, goddamn it!
You win!
Fuck you, motherfucker!
My ass! Die
[PANTS]
AUGUSTUS: [ON VIDEO CALL]
Hayden.
Oh, fuck, Hayden.
Listen, Hayden.
I didn't have a choice.
Hayden, the client demanded it.
Hayden. Hayden.
[BIRDS SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
[WATER LAPPING]
[♪♪♪]
[BLOOD PLOPPING]
[WATER RIPPLING]
[GUN HAMMER CLICKS]
[♪♪♪]
Hello, Sam.
Like seein' a ghost? I know.
You're not real.
Of course I am.
Mm-mm-mm-mm.
How?
Augustus used me to recruit you.
He knew we would hit it off,
as they say.
After all, with what happened
with your parents,
you were the perfect candidate
for training.
I killed you.
[LAUGHS]
Sam, please.
You couldn't even do that right.
You missed my heart.
[GUNSHOT]
[BODY THUDS]
[COUGHS]
Nona, for the last six years,
I've been talking to your ghost.
Sounds like you need
a shrink to me.
You shot the woman you loved.
I was never okay with it. Never.
Pathetico.
Where's Managold, Sam?
Dead.
Come on, Sam.
We had some
good times together, didn't we?
You can tell me the truth.
I am telling you the truth.
Liar.
It's fitting, you killing me.
It's how it's supposed to be.
At least you get to die
at your lake, right?
That's what you always wanted.
-[BULLET ZINGS]
-[GUNSHOT]
[BODY THUDS]
[BIRDS SINGING IN BACKGROUND]
[♪♪♪]
[PHONE RINGING]
Racing's finished for the day
if you were plannin'
on making any bets.
[CHARLES ON PHONE]
That's your line of work,
not mine.
I'm always happy to hear it
from my best asset.
CHARLES: [ON PHONE]
I'm not yours anymore.
Come on. Come on in.
Let's talk about this.
I have one more job for you,
and then we're even.
You've got my word.
CHARLES: [ON PHONE]
Your word?
Managold, you know
my word's always good.
CHARLES: [ON PHONE]
Yeah, I guess.
It's a special job.
CHARLES: [ON PHONE]
Hayden.
You want me to kill the man
who let me live?
The man that failed to kill you?
Yes!
And think about it.
The legend
comes out of retirement
to take down
the killer of all killers.
You do this,
and I'll make sure you
and your family are good
from now on.
[CHARLES ON PHONE]
I nteresting offer, but,
I called to say goodbye.
Let's think about this
for a second.
[CHARLES ON PHONE]
I've been doin'
a lot of thinkin'.
You know what happens next.
CHARLES: [ON PHONE]
I do. Goodbye, Augustus.
[SIGHS]
[BANG]
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
[SAM ON PHONE] You
have somethin' on your shirt.
Excuse me?
You should have bet
on a sure thing.
Oh, fuck.
[GUNSHOT]
[CAR DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS]
[♪♪♪]
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
[CAR WHIRS]
SAM: Remember when I said
you can't have friends
in this business?
Turns out it's all bullshit.
In this world,
you need friends.
[♪♪♪]